Now, everyone, deliver! Poka poka street dance cola and singing songs!
Let's spread it out! Coke Tea Series!
In the wide world, you found the sarin for immortality
I have nothing to see, but you have given me a lot of color.
Thank you so much!
Hiro to let me! Corati Series
Part 1
Naccho's graduation sale on the first day of the NICCA show
That's right.
How's it going?
Well, I'm still getting a feel for it.
I think it's too late.
Nothing special has changed.
The everyday life that I loved so much is still here today.
Because there's no change at all
I honestly don't feel it at all.
But all of the members are very supportive of me.
They conveyed their feelings to me.
I felt warmth from them.
I love it so much!
I'll be there!
Please take care of me!
Hey, Kun-chan!
How did it go? The rehearsal...
Rehearsal? Is this a rehearsal?
Last rehearsal?
Last rehearsal.
But everyone's still there, just the same.
We're going to eat.
I'm relieved.
No change?
We're still here, but...
But you're gone.
Don't be so sad.
I'm not in Yokogawa.
I miss you.
I hate to see this day end.
Thank you.
This is the captain's group who helped me a lot.
To the members.
I have a letter for you.
I brought you something that belongs to the captains.
I'm so embarrassed.
I don't think I can tell you.
He wrote back.
Thank you.
No problem.
Gamelan?
No, what hooray. No, what hooray is
Christmas.
ornament.
What's the pattern?
Strawberry
A ghost.
It's all the same, different patterns.
Strawberry ghost.
Thank you.
I don't know.
What's this? It's cute.
Cute.
It's so cute.
Strawberry ghost.
I really don't know.
I'm so happy
Strawberry ghost
I see
Candles and a Christmas tree
I'm so happy!
I love this kind of thing
My psyllium crown
Thank you so much!
Thank you so much.
A lot. a lot.
How does it feel to be told you don't want to do something?
It's like...
I didn't know people thought that much of me.
Think about it.
You do it.
Don't do it.
You've told me more than anyone.
He came in here today angry.
I have to be angry or I'll cry.
Get mad at me today.
Why?
I saw him again today.
You scared me.
I don't know what's wrong.
I don't know.
I thought she'd cry.
I thought I would cry.
I always use mascara
I always use mascara that comes off with hot water.
but this time I used waterproof mascara.
I'm sure I'm going to cry
I know I'm going to cry.
If I cry at "Silent Lover"...
Solo phat.
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah...
I just met Nibu.
I met Nibu-chan.
Nibu was all smiles.
She said she came to see me off.
I'll do my best.
I'm begging you.
I'm your silent lover.
Cry.
I'm going to try something.
I've done some tests.
I've tried...
I really love you guys.
No, not yet.
Through the live show.
I hope that I can convey a lot
I hope I can convey
I hope I can convey a lot to you. Thank you and I love you.
I would like to convey my thanks and love to the members first
Thank you very much.
I look forward to working with you.
Shall we play the role?
Yes, ma'am.
Okay, well, I'll tell you what.
What can we do with this group? This is the last time we can do it with this group.
Today is the last time we will be able to do this together.
Let's all enjoy the stage.
Enjoy the stage
Let's have no regrets today.
Let's spend the day with no regrets.
Seino
Let's have a day with no regrets for those guys
I'm going to spend it
One, two, three.
Guys! Everyone!
Thank you very much for coming to Inatakozaka46 Happy Goreinfar 2020 today.
I am Sakira Ishio from Inatakozaka 46.
My name is Sei Okada.
Yes, thank you very much.
Please wait a moment, and I would like to inform you of a request.
Cameras and video cameras in the remodeling,
cameras, video cameras, binoculars with graffiti, and other filming and recording equipment.
Please refrain from using them.
also in the auditorium.
Oh, sorry.
That was fast.
Please refrain from using cell phones in the auditorium
Please note that it may take some time before the end of the year.
Thank you for your understanding in advance.
The show will begin shortly. The show will begin shortly.
Salina, I love you and I will always love you and I will always love you.
Thank you.
You're happy?
I'm going to fill you with happiness.
Good night.
If you think I'm a masochist...
I'm so happy to see you all here.
I've met so many of you over the past eight years.
You are very important to me.
You have been so necessary to me.
You have given me a lot of color, even though I have nothing to show for it.
Thank you so very, very much.
I wish you all a happy life from now on.
I wish you all happiness.
Thank you so much!
They've sent out all kinds of letters.
Goods too. Thank you.
Purple and yellow.
What? Really.
I didn't notice.
That's amazing.
Thank you very much.
This is really the kind of place, isn't it?
The sun is kind to people. The sun is kind to you.
I am really happy. Thank you very much.
We, the second term students, were invited by many Yachosan and came here.
This time that we were able to work together with Yacho-san is something that I really can't hold up.
Congratulations on your graduation.
Thank you very much.
And, thank you very much,
It's wonderful.
Amazing.
Thank you very much.
Please come to the stage, thank you very much for your visit.
Thank you.
I'll do my best. I'll do my best. I'll do my best a little bit more.
I'll do my best for Tadasaka's activities.
When I see you again from afar
I will do my best so that you will think that I have become stronger.
Thank you for always being there for me when I'm having a hard time.
I look forward to working with you in the future.
Thank you for being my friend.
Thank you very much.
Well, thank you so much for everything.
I'll be your grandfather's grandfather.
Thank you.
One, two, three. One, two, three.
Cute.
Cute little princess.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for your hard work
So let's have a toast.
Cheers.
Thank you for your hard work.
You must be happy.
Oh, it's a little heavy, a little big
Thank you very much. Bon appétit.
Wow!
Amazing!
Thank you so much. Surrounded by my favorite people, singing my favorite songs, and standing on my favorite stage, I think those days are my treasures,
I love you all even more, and I was really very happy.
I am so happy and I love you all even more.
Thank you so very much. I was very happy.